https://www.legallanguage.com/privacy/

Privacy Policy
Legal Language Services respects your privacy and security. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise share your personal information, such as name, email address, physical address, phone numbers, buying history, etc. without your permission.
At any time you may contact Legal Language Services with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes.
How We Protect Your Information
Your access to some services and content is password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Legal Language Service will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. You should not disclose your user name and password to others.
Free QuoteGet your FREE price quote today!Get Quote Now!
Get a QuoteYour Name *Phone *CompanyEmail *Click here to view our Privacy PolicyWhat Service(s) Do You Need? *Document TranslationOn-site InterpretingRemote InterpretingInternational Service of ProcessEvidence Taking AbroadVerbatim TranscriptionMultilingual DiscoveryTransportationMultimedia (e.g. Voiceover, Subtitling)check all that applyRequested Delivery Date (Estimate) *Source Language (From): *AfarAfrikaansAkanAlbanianAmharicArabicAramaicArmenianAshantiAymar·AzerbaijaniBafutBahasaBambaraBasqueBassaBelarussianBembaBengaliBislamaBlackfootBosnianBretonBulgarianBurmeseCajunCambodianCantoneseCatalanCebuanoChamoroChichewaChineseChinookCreoleCroatianCrowCzechDanishDariDhivehiDutchDzongkhaEdoEnglishEstonianEweFaroeseFarsiFijianFijian HindiFilipinoFinnishFlemishFrenchFrisianFulaniFuuta JalonGaGaelicGalicianGeorgianGermanGikuyuGreekGreenlandicGuaranÌGujaratiHausaHawaiianHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIboIcelandicIlocanoIlonggoIndonesianItalianJapaneseJolaKannadaKarenKazakhKhalkha MongolKhmerKinyarwandaKirghizKirundiKissiKiswahiliKoniaguiKonoKoreanKurdishKwanyamaKyrgyzLaotianLatinLatvianLiberianLingalaLithuanianLuxemburgianMacedonianMalagasyMalayMalayalamMalinkeMalteseMandarinMandingoMandinkaMaoriMarathiMarshalleseMirandeseMoldovanMongolianNauruanNavajoNdebeleNepaliNiueanNorwegianNzemaOriyaOromoOssetianOtetelaPalauanPapiamentoPashtuPolishPolynesianPortugueseProvencalPunjabiPushtuQuechuaRomanianRussianSamoanSanskritScotsSerbianSesothoSign LanguageSign Language - AmericanSindhiSinhalaSinhaleseSiouxSlovakSlovenianSomaliSoninkeSpanishSrananSwahiliSwatiSwedishTagalogTaiwaneseTajikTamilTeluguTetumThaiTibetanTigrignaTokelauanTonganTurkishTurkmanTuvaluanTwiTzotzilUkrainianUrduUzbekValencianVietnameseVlaamsWallisianWelshWolofXhosaYanomamiYiddishYorubaZarmaZuluOtherTarget Language (To): *AfarAfrikaansAkanAlbanianAmharicArabicAramaicArmenianAshantiAymar·AzerbaijaniBafutBahasaBambaraBasqueBassaBelarussianBembaBengaliBislamaBlackfootBosnianBretonBulgarianBurmeseCajunCambodianCantoneseCatalanCebuanoChamoroChichewaChineseChinookCreoleCroatianCrowCzechDanishDariDhivehiDutchDzongkhaEdoEnglishEstonianEweFaroeseFarsiFijianFijian HindiFilipinoFinnishFlemishFrenchFrisianFulaniFuuta JalonGaGaelicGalicianGeorgianGermanGikuyuGreekGreenlandicGuaranÌGujaratiHausaHawaiianHebrewHindiHmongHungarianIboIcelandicIlocanoIlonggoIndonesianItalianJapaneseJolaKannadaKarenKazakhKhalkha MongolKhmerKinyarwandaKirghizKirundiKissiKiswahiliKoniaguiKonoKoreanKurdishKwanyamaKyrgyzLaotianLatinLatvianLiberianLingalaLithuanianLuxemburgianMacedonianMalagasyMalayMalayalamMalinkeMalteseMandarinMandingoMandinkaMaoriMarathiMarshalleseMirandeseMoldovanMongolianNauruanNavajoNdebeleNepaliNiueanNorwegianNzemaOriyaOromoOssetianOtetelaPalauanPapiamentoPashtuPolishPolynesianPortugueseProvencalPunjabiPushtuQuechuaRomanianRussianSamoanSanskritScotsSerbianSesothoSign LanguageSign Language - AmericanSindhiSinhalaSinhaleseSiouxSlovakSlovenianSomaliSoninkeSpanishSrananSwahiliSwatiSwedishTagalogTaiwaneseTajikTamilTeluguTetumThaiTibetanTigrignaTokelauanTonganTurkishTurkmanTuvaluanTwiTzotzilUkrainianUrduUzbekValencianVietnameseVlaamsWallisianWelshWolofXhosaYanomamiYiddishYorubaZarmaZuluOtherCountry *Where Are You Located? (required)United StatesAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaAruba (the Netherlands)AustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermuda (UK)BhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBritish Virgin Islands (UK)BruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurmaBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman Islands (UK)Central African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandColombiaComorosCongoCongo Dem. Rep. ofCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuracao (The Netherlands)CyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEngland (UK)Equatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas) (UK)Faroe IslandsFiji IslandsFinlandFranceFrench Guyana (France)French PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltar (UK)GreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupe (France)GuamGuatemalaGuernsy (UK)GuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong Kong† (SAR PRC)HungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of Man (UK)IsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJersey (UK)JordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (North)Korea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao (SAR PRC)MacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartinique (France)MauritaniaMauritiusMayotte IslandMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMongolia (PRC)MontenegroMontserrat (UK)MoroccoMozambiqueNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Ireland (UK)Northern Marianas IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn (UK)PolandPortugalPuerto Rico (US)QatarReunion Island (France)RomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint Maarten (Netherlands Antilles)Saint Martin (France)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaScotland (UK)SenegalSerbiaSeychelles RepublicSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSt. Helena (UK)St. Kitts/NevisSt. LuciaSt. Pierre and MiquelonSt. Vincent and GrenadinesSudanSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos Islands (UK)TuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (US)Wake IslandWales (UK)Wallis and Futuna IslandsYemenZambiaZimbabweDestination Country *Where Will Services Take Place? (required)United StatesAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaAruba (the Netherlands)AustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermuda (UK)BhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBritish Virgin Islands (UK)BruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurmaBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman Islands (UK)Central African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandColombiaComorosCongoCongo Dem. Rep. ofCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuracao (The Netherlands)CyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEngland (UK)Equatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas) (UK)Faroe IslandsFiji IslandsFinlandFranceFrench Guyana (France)French PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltar (UK)GreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupe (France)GuamGuatemalaGuernsy (UK)GuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasHong Kong† (SAR PRC)HungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of Man (UK)IsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJersey (UK)JordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (North)Korea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao (SAR PRC)MacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartinique (France)MauritaniaMauritiusMayotte IslandMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMongolia (PRC)MontenegroMontserrat (UK)MoroccoMozambiqueNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Ireland (UK)Northern Marianas IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn (UK)PolandPortugalPuerto Rico (US)QatarReunion Island (France)RomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint Maarten (Netherlands Antilles)Saint Martin (France)SamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaScotland (UK)SenegalSerbiaSeychelles RepublicSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSt. Helena (UK)St. Kitts/NevisSt. LuciaSt. Pierre and MiquelonSt. Vincent and GrenadinesSudanSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos Islands (UK)TuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands (US)Wake IslandWales (UK)Wallis and Futuna IslandsYemenZambiaZimbabweWill you be uploading a document /file to your request? *NoYesNumber of files to upload *1234Attach as many as 4 digital files.
* If you have more than 4 files or files that exceed 5MB each, we will provide you with password-protected access for uploading to our FTP site.
Also, you can email the files to us directly at getaquote@legallanguage.com.1. File Upload *
Click or drag a file to this area to upload.
Allowed file extensions: .doc, .xls, .csv, .pdf, .txt, .docx,
.xlsx2. File Upload *
Click or drag a file to this area to upload.
Allowed file extensions: .doc, .xls, .csv, .pdf, .txt, .docx, .xlsx3. File Upload
*
Click or drag a file to this area to upload.
Allowed file extensions: .doc, .xls, .csv, .pdf, .txt, .docx, .xlsx4. File Upload
*
Click or drag a file to this area to upload.
Allowed file extensions: .doc, .xls, .csv, .pdf, .txt, .docx, .xlsxNotes & Other Requirements *WebsiteRequest Quote
Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Email Address
First Name
Last Name
Select One Newsletter:
In Brief: Legal Analysis of Recent Case Law
Amicus Briefs: General Interest Newsletter
Leave this field empty if you're human:
Recent Posts
How Not to Respond to Defective Service in Family Law Litigation
December 2, 2020
Are You Legally Required to Translate Consumer Contracts?
November 20, 2020
A Cautionary Tale on Using Local Counsel to Serve Process: A Case Study from Latvia
November 9, 2020
Quick LinksFrequently Asked Questions
Testimonials
How-to Guides & Forms
Employment Opportunities
Transportation Registration
Privacy Policy
Copyright Notice
Disclaimer The information contained on this website is provided for informational purposes only, and should not be construed as legal advice on any matter.
Contact Info
15 Maiden Lane, Suite 300 New York, NY 10038 USA1-800-755-5775Int'l Call: 001 (913) 341-3167getaquote@legallanguage.comhttps://www.legallanguage.com
